cyloop.com 2010-11-21

# Privacy Policy

We at Cyloop are committed to maintaining your privacy. This privacy policy and agreement ('Privacy Policy') covers how we collect, use, and treat personal information that you may provide through our websites (the 'Website' or the 'Site') or while participating in the services we offer at the Website (the 'Services'). The terms 'you' and 'your' refer to any visitor to the Website, including (i) casual visitors to our Site, who do not participate in the Services ('Site Visitors'), (ii) musicians, musical groups, visual artists, videographers, and video and sound recording mixers and producers, and other participants in the music or video industries, who visit the Site to promote, introduce, and air their works ('Contributing Artists '); and (iii) users who create profiles, enjoy the music and audio-visual works of our Contributing Artists, and otherwise participate in our Services ('Members'). The terms 'Cyloop', 'we' and 'us' refer to Cyloop, LLC and Cyloop.com. 

###  1\. Your Consent 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully; once you consent to this Policy's terms, it creates legal obligations on you and on Cyloop. We ask you to show your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy in different ways, depending on your relationship to the Site. The procedures for consenting to this Policy are (a) less formal if you are simply a casual Site Visitor, and (b) more formal if you are seeking to become a Member or a Contributing Artist featured on the Site.   

####  1.1. Consent by Site Visitors. 

By accessing and using our Website as a Site Visitor, you are acknowledging that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy and agree to be legally bound by it. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please refrain from using our Site.By accessing and using our Website as a Site Visitor, you are acknowledging that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy and agree to be legally bound by it. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please refrain from using our Site. 

####  1.2. Consent by Contributing Artists and Members. 

If you register as a Contributing Artist or a Member, you will be prompted to click an 'I Accept' button linked to this Policy during the registration process. Clicking 'I accept' confirms your agreement to be bound by this Privacy Policy. 

###  2\. Participation by Children and Teens; Advisory 

Due to the nature of communications that may take place on our Site, and due to federal policy in favor of protecting children under 13 years of age (as reflected in the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), WE DO NOT ALLOW INDIVIDUALS WHO WE KNOW ARE UNDER 13 TO PARTICIPATE IN OUR SITE OR SERVICES. Please understand that we cannot necessarily tell if a user is providing us with his or her true age. 

YOU MUST BE AT LEAST 13 YEARS OLD TO USE OUR SITE AND SERVICES. BECAUSE THE SERVICE MAY PROVIDE ACCESS TO CONTENT THAT CONTAINS EXPLICIT MATERIAL (SUCH AS STRONG LANGUAGE OR DEPICTIONS OF SEX, VIOLENCE, OR SUBSTANCE ABUSE), PARENTAL DISCRETION IS ADVISED FOR ALL USERS AGED 13 TO 17. 

IF YOU ARE BETWEEN 13 AND 17 YEARS OF AGE, PLEASE REVIEW THIS AGREEMENT WITH YOUR PARENT OR GUARDIAN. 

###  3\. The Types Of Information You May Provide 

Information you may provide while visiting our Site or while participating in our Services falls into two broad categories: (i) personally identifiable information, and (ii) aggregate information. We use the term 'Personally Identifiable Information' to mean any information that could reasonably be used to identify you, including your name, address, e-mail address, birth date, financial information, photograph, telephone number or any combination of information that could be used to identify you. 'Anonymous Information' is information that does not identify you, and may include statistical information concerning, for example, your use of our Services, your access to works by our Contributing Artists, or the pages on our Site that you visit most frequently. These two categories of information can be further divided into (iii) information that we collect from, and that you provide to us ('Site-Directed Information'), and (iv) information you intend to provide or make available to other Members on our Site ('Member-Directed Information'). Our Privacy Policy governs all Site-Directed Information - whether this information is personally identifiable information or anonymous information - and does not govern Member-Directed Information, as we have no direct control over the collection or use of Member-Directed Information. 

###  4\. Site-Directed Personally Identifiable Information; Our Uses Of This Information 

We will not share personally identifiable information you provide to us via the Website with any third party, other than as expressly disclosed in this policy. We collect information from Site Visitors, Members, and Contributing Artists at different points on our Website and through our Services, and use this information as follows: 

####  4.1. Registration Information; User Names. 

In order to participate as a Member or Contributing Artist in our Services, we require that you complete a registration form. This form asks for contact information, which includes such items as (i) name; (ii) mailing address; (iii) birth date (for COPPA and eligibility purposes); (iv) gender; and (v) email address. The registration process provides Members and Contributing Artists with a user name and password, which allow them to gain access to the Website and Services to which they have subscribed. Our system relies on user names as the public 'identifier' for the particular Member. 

####  4.2. Band Information. 

If you register your musical group with our Site as a Contributing Artist, you will be asked to provide us with the first and last names of all band members, and gender of all band members. In addition, we ask that you provide a 'biography' of your band. These names and the biography will be made available on your band's profile page (gender information will remain private). You may provide additional information about your band for on your band profile, as you choose. 

####  4.3. Email Addresses. 

We use your e-mail address to send notifications relating to our Site, including for example, to confirm when one Member has requested to add you as a friend, to provide notice that a Member has received a message or comment from you, and to invite new friends to join Cyloop.com. In addition, to facilitate locating friends, you can search for particular Members' profiles by using their full name or e-mail address. Our search features are structured to that you must first know your friend's full name or email address in order to locate their profile. 

####  4.4. Invitations to Third Parties. 

Members and Contributing Artists are able, at our Site, to use our 'invitation service' to inform friends about their profiles, and to encourage friends to register at our Site. If you choose to request such a invitation, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will then send the friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We store the information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email, and the friend may contact us in accordance with Section 10 (Changing or Removing Information; Opting Out) to request the removal of this information from our databases. 

####  4.5. Communications with Other Members. 

In registering under the Website, Members and Contributing Artists indicate an interest in exchanging information with other Members, subject to any Privacy Controls imposed. To allow such communications, we provide information to identify individual users, in the form of Members' and Contributing Artists' user names. We seek to limit the information provided through our system to the minimum information needed to identify a participant in communications and other exchanges. 

####  4.6. Other Information Exchanges. 

The Website allows Members and Contributing Artists (i) to provide and receive information in a range of forms on an unlimited number of topics, and (ii) to engage in other activity through Website discussions that may include, at the option of the user, an exchange of personally identifiable information. In these instances, we use any information you provide to us strictly for the purposes for which you submit the information. 

####  4.7. Use of Profiles in Promotions. 

We believe that our Members' own experiences on the Site can often act as the strongest promotion for the Site and our Services. To promote and illustrate our Services and the Site, therefore, we may wish to post on our Home Page, and in other areas of the Site, profiles and other Content of our Members. We assume that Members who choose not to employ our Privacy Controls are interested in (or do not object to) publicizing their profiles and related Content. If we have used your profile or other information for these purposes, and you do not wish us to do so, please notify us as provided in Section 16 (Contact Us). If personally identifiable information is involved, we will remove the information from our promotional material, within a reasonable period of time. 

####  4.8. Informational Notices and Bulletins. 

Periodically, we may choose to send news, bulletins, marketing materials, or other information to Members and Contributing Artists, and will use personally identifiable information to send such communications. If we choose to undertake such communications, you will have the ability to opt out of receiving these communications as provided in Section 12 (Changing or Removing Information; Opting Out). 

####  4.9. Bulletin Boards and Chat Rooms. 

As one of our Services, we offer a bulletin board system (BBS) and chat rooms on our Site. We make only your user name available to other users of these services. Any comments you contribute to the online dialogue, however, become public immediately, attributed to your user name. You should, therefore, use discretion in what you submit to these exchanges. 

####  4.10. Surveys and Contests. 

Periodically, we may initiate surveys or contests at Cyloop.com, and we may request personally identifiable information from you in connection with such surveys and contests. You are free to choose whether you participate in a survey or contest. The information we request may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and this information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and appeal of this Site. We will notify you of relevant details in connection with asking for you participation in such surveys or contests. 

###  5\. Your Responsibility for Member-Directed Information 

Member-Directed Information is information you intend to provide or make available to other Members or Contributing Artists on our Site. Although we counsel you to take care if you include personally identifiable information in your Member-Directed Information, our Privacy Policy does not cover Member-Directed Information. If you choose to disclose any personally identifiable information, any such information can be collected and used by other Members or users, and you may receive unsolicited communications as a result. We provide a range of Services to assist you in making good choices concerning the information you disclose. Please see Section 9 (Further Tools for Protecting Your Privacy) for a description. 

###  6\. Anonymous, Aggregate Information 

. 

We use Anonymous Information to analyze the effectiveness of our Site, to improve our Services, and for other similar purposes, including for purposes of generating Artist Reports for our Contributing Artists. In addition, from time to time, we may undertake or commission statistical and other summary analyses of the general behavior and characteristics of users participating in our Services and the characteristics of visitors at our Site, and may share Anonymous Information with third parties. Rest assured, though, that Anonymous Information provided to third parties will not allow anyone to identify you, or determine anything personal about you. We may collect Anonymous Information through features of the software that supports our Services, through cookies, and through other means described below. 

####  6.1. IP Addresses; Logs. 

Hoodiny may automatically receive and record information in our server logs from your browser, including your IP address (the Internet address of your PC), your computer's name, the type and version of your web browser, referrer addresses and other generally-accepted log information. We may also record page views (hit counts) and other general statistical and tracking information, which will be aggregated with that of other users in order to understand how our Website is being used, and for security and monitoring purposes. None of this data contains personally identifiable information. 

####  6.2. Cookies. 

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a website's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be used to provide you with a tailored user experience and to make it easier for you to use a website upon a future visit. We may include cookies on our Website and use them to recognize you when you return to our Website. You may set your browser so that it does not accept cookies. Cookies must be enabled on your web browser, however, if you wish to access certain personalized features of our Services. 

####  6.3. Tags. 

We may use so-called 'pixel tags' - small graphic images (also know as 'web beacons' or 'single-pixel GIFS') - to tell us what parts of our website have been visited or to measure the effectiveness of searches customers perform on our Site. Pixel tags also enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read, and they inform us whether emails have been opened, to help ensure that our messages are of interest to our Members and Contributing Artists. None of this data includes personally identifiable information, and you can 'opt-out' of receiving these types of emails from us by following the directions provided in Section 10 (Changing or Removing Information; Opting Out). If any personally identifiable information is collected using such tools, it will be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

####  6.4. Click-Throughs. 

We may send email messages which use a 'click-through URL' linked to content on our Website. When you click one of these URLs, you pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. We tracks this click-through data to help determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked simply do not click text or graphic links in the email, or notify us in accordance with Section 10 (Changing or Removing Information; Opting Out). 

####  6.5. Banner Ads. 

The Services may include the use of ad banner partners for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions, and other marketing messages. These ads may be provided, in some cases, by a third party ad service provider or advertiser ('Advertisers'). The Advertiser may place or utilize its own cookie on your browser, and may use Anonymous Information about your visit to our sites, such as the number of times you have viewed the ad. If the Advertiser requests personally identifiable information from you, please be aware that this Advertiser's use and collection of this information will be governed by its own privacy policy, and not our Policy. We recommend that you review the Advertiser's privacy policy before providing personally identifiable information. 

####  6.6. Computer Configuration. 

In order to determine whether your computer is supported by our system, we may collect certain Anonymous Information. This information includes, but may not be limited to, your operating system and browser, as well as the presence of any software that our Website may require to operate with your computer, or other third party software on your computer. This information is kept strictly confidential and is not shared with third parties, except as provided for in this Privacy Policy. 

###  7\. Any Information Linked With Your Personally Identifiable Information Is Protected As 'Personally Identifiable Information' 

To enable us to better understand the characteristics of our Customers and/or to provide services tailored to your needs, we may link (a) the personally identifiable information you have provided; with (b) Anonymous Information. If we combine or link any Anonymous Information or other information with your personally identifiable information, the resulting combination will be treated and protected as personally identifiable information under this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, no unrelated third parties will have access to this information, and any of our service providers who are granted access to this information will be bound to protect it in accordance with this Policy. 

###  8\. We Do Not Disclose Site-Directed, Personally Identifiable Information to Unaffiliated Third Parties; Limited Exceptions 

We will not disclose your personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties without your express consent, except in the following limited circumstances: 

####  8.1. Cyloop Site Vendors. 

We may employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf, such as maintaining the Website, providing services related to the Site, collecting information, responding to and sending electronic mail, or other functions necessary to our business. We may need to share your personally identifiable information with these companies (collectively, 'Site Vendors'). We will provide Site Vendors with only that information necessary to perform their functions, and we will not allow them to use your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

####  8.2. Imminent Harm. 

We may reveal your personally identifiable information to attorneys, private investigator organizations or law enforcement agencies if we believe (a) that you are in risk of harm from another, or (b) that you are harming or interfering (or will imminently harm or interfere) with others or violating (either intentionally or unintentionally) our Terms and Conditions of Use or otherwise violating legal rights. 

####  8.3. Legal. 

Hoodiny will reveal your personally identifiable information, to the extent we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law. If we receive legal process calling for the disclosure of your personally identifiable information we will attempt to notify you via the email address you supplied during registration within a reasonable amount of time before we respond to the request, unless such notification is not permitted. 

####  8.4. Transfer of Site. 

Hoodiny shall be entitled to transfer to a third party information it collects, including any personally identifiable information, in connection with a sale of all or substantially all of the assets of the business entity responsible for the information under this Policy, provided the acquiring third party has agreed to safeguard your personally identifiable information with protections that in all material respects are the same as or more protective than those set out in this Privacy Policy. 

###  9\. Additional Tools for Protecting Your Privacy 

We recognize that children and other users may provide more personal information than they intend, or should, over the public areas in social networking sites. We provide a range of Services to assist our Members seeking to preserve an appropriate level of privacy, including the following: 

####  9.1. Privacy Controls. 

We provide you with privacy controls, that allow you to designate your complete profile, or portions of you profile, as 'closed' to all but certain specified Members and Contributing Artists (our 'Privacy Controls'). Please either employ the Privacy Controls, or choose carefully the information you post on your profile, and that you provide to other Members. You should take care if you choose to include information that personally identifies you, such as your telephone number, street address, last name, email address, and any geographically recognizable photographs. 

####  9.2. Role of Parents. 

Access to Information.We encourage parents and children to talk about the proper treatment of personal information online. To further encourage this dialogue, and in light of the parent-child legal relationship, we will provide to parents (or the guardian) of a Member who is under 18 the same access rights we provide to the Member at issue (as set out in Section 10 (Changing or Removing Information; Opting Out)), provided we have been given sufficient information to verify that the individuals making the request are, in fact, the parents or the guardian of the Member (a 'Teen Member Parent'). 

####  9.3. Removing a Profile. 

If you are a Teen Member Parent, and want your child's profile removed from our Site (you must remove your child's profile if they are under 13), we suggest that you first ask your child to remove it him or herself. If your child is unwilling to remove the profile, you may remove the profile in accordance with Section 10 (Changing or Removing Information; Opting Out). 

####  9.4. Reporting of Problems. 

If you feel that you or one of your friends have been harassed or bullied on our Site, or that users have infringed on your privacy or violated our Code of Conduct, please report your concerns, as set out in our Terms and Conditions of Use. 

###  10\. Changing or Removing Information; Opting Out. 

####  10.1. Discretionary Account Information. 

To allow appropriate control over personally identifiable information, you can access your account (after supplying your user name and password) to change or update discretionary information that you have previously submitted. 

####  10.2. Opt-Out. 

If we choose to send to you bulletins, updates, or other unsolicited communications that are marketing-related materials, we will provide you with the ability to decline -- or 'opt-out of' - receiving such communications. Instructions for opting-out will be provided if and when we determine to send you such a communication. Please understand that you will not be allowed to 'opt-out' of formal notices concerning operation of this Website, and legal and other related notices concerning your relationship to the Site. 

####  10.3. Deleting Information. 

Finally, if you request, we will remove your name and all other personally identifiable information from our databases. Please understand, however, that it may be impossible to remove this information completely, due to backups and records of deletions. In addition, please understand that, if you request deletion of your information, you will be unable to utilize associated features of the Website and any associated Services. You may not remove de-identified, anonymous, or aggregate data from our databases. 

####  10.4. Parental Review 

A parent or guardian of a Member who is aged 13 through 17 (a 'Teen Member Parent') is entitled to review the information that we have collected from or concerning their child (or ward), withdraw their consent to our further use of such information, or direct the deletion of such information by contacting us in accordance with Section 16 (Contact Us). 

###  11\. Security 

We have put in place security systems designed to prevent unauthorized access to or disclosure of personally identifiable Site-Directed Information you provide to us, and we take all reasonable steps to secure and safeguard this Information. Our site's password-protected section requires users to give us unique identifiers such as their user id and password. Moreover, we store all Site-Directed personally identifiable information we receive on a separate system, designed to be secure and isolated from direct connection to the Internet. Hoodiny employees (and employees of our affiliates and Site Vendors) are required to acknowledge that they understand and will abide by our policies with respect to the confidentiality of personally identifiable information. Moreover, we provide access to our databases containing personally identifiable information on a need-to-know basis only. 

Our security systems are therefore structured to deter and prevent hackers and others from accessing information you provide to us. We also use software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Please understand, though, that this information should not be construed in any way as giving business, legal, or other advice, or warranting as fail proof, the security of information provided by or submitted to Hoodiny. Due to the nature of Internet communications and evolving technologies, we cannot provide, and disclaim, assurance that the information you provide us will remain free from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties who, despite our efforts, obtain unauthorized access. 

###  12\. Notice of Security Incident 

If we detect, despite the safeguards set out above, an intrusion or other unauthorized access to or use of personally identifiable information (an 'Intrusion'), we will (i) notify effected users of the Intrusion if the information at issue is sensitive, in our discretion, (ii) deliver this notice by the means we deem most efficient under the circumstances (such as, for example, first class mail or email); (iii) use contact information for each effected user that is current in our files; and (iv) use commercially reasonable efforts to accomplish these steps and effect this notice in a timely manner. To the extent applicable law requires steps in addition to those specified above, we will under all circumstances comply with applicable law. 

###  13\. Notification of Changes 

From time to time, Hoodiny may change its Privacy Policy. If we make any changes regarding disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties, we will attempt to contact you prior to the date the modified policy is scheduled to take effect. We will post notice of the new Policy from the privacy link on our Website. With respect to Site Visitors, your use of our Site following any such change constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by the Privacy Policy, as changed. With respect to Members and Contributing Artists, no such changes will take effect unless and until you have provided us with your consent to such changes, in accordance with Sections 1.2 or Section 1.3, above. 

###  14\. Relationship to Terms of Use and Other Contracts 

This Privacy Policy must be read in conjunction with our Terms and Conditions of Use, and the provisions of our Terms and Conditions of Use are incorporated herein. To the extent the Terms and Conditions of Use conflict with the terms of this Privacy Policy, the terms of this Privacy Policy will control. 

###  15\. Further Resources 

###  16\. Contact Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us at: 

Attention: President   
Hoodiny Entertainment Group, LLC   
555 Washington Ave., Suite 340   
Miami Beach, FL 33139   

###  17\. Effective Date 

The effective date of this Privacy Policy is August 27, 2007.
